<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Luchanworld</title><link>https://luchanworld.com/</link><description>Recent content on Luchanworld</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 20:29:37 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luchanworld.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mindfulness</title><link>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2021-01/mindfulness/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 20:29:37 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2021-01/mindfulness/</guid><description>Sustainable Travel Reducing Your Vacation’s Impact Is Easier Than You Think Pack light: Less luggage means a reduction in carbon emissions released into the atmosphere by your plane. Whilst it might not compensate for the flight itself, it can help!
Protect the environment Bring a reusable utensil sets, a refillable water bottle and a water filter so you don’t have to waste plastic. Besides, it’s cheaper too.
Minimise single-use plastic altogether: Ditch the single use plastic miniatures by switching to solid shampoo and conditioner, solid soap, bamboo toothbrush, bamboo comb and toothpaste tablets.
Choose the most environmentally friendly form of transport. Can you drive or take the train to your destination instead of flying? Try to especially avoid short haul (&amp;lt; 500 km) flights, and if you must fly, choose airlines with higher occupancy rates and more efficient aircraft.
Minimize your carbon emissions and pollution: try to book direct flights and keep domestic flights at a minimum
Support the local economy Stay with locals for an authentic experience - find a homestay or AirBnB
When possible, support family-owned local businesses that employ local people rather than large international companies
Hire a local guide! After all, they know their home country better than anyone</description></item><item><title>First time in Europe</title><link>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2019-03/first-time-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 10:07:33 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2019-03/first-time-in-europe/</guid><description>Try to be the best version of yourself every day</description></item><item><title>Korea</title><link>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2019-03/korea/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 11:02:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2019-03/korea/</guid><description>Try to be the best version of yourself every day</description></item><item><title>Thailand</title><link>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2019-03/thailand/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 11:02:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2019-03/thailand/</guid><description>Try to be the best version of yourself every day</description></item><item><title>Beginning</title><link>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2019-03/beginning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 12:53:37 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://luchanworld.com/blog/2019-03/beginning/</guid><description>Try to be the best version of yourself every day</description></item></channel></rss>